Hi, my name is Ryan.
Hi, my name is Tensae Laki.
And we're both Columbia students studying computer science.
Today we built Liquid, a seller's tool
to sell products extremely fast.
Imagine you have a bottle that you want to sell,
but don't really have the time or capacity to do that.
You can just text Liquid
and it will sort everything out for you.
First, all you have to do is just submit a picture of it
and describe it in a few sentences,
and then you will have a listing in under five minutes.
Nice, yeah.
And so how it works is OpenAI Vision
identifies the item,
and then an image model produces the listing photo,
which is redefined and just a little touched up
so users can see what the item actually looks like.
And then a second call compares it against the original
and blocks any edit changes that could have been bad
or deceitful because we wanted people
to see what real products look like.
And then Apify pulls sold
and active daily eBay comps.
So it can basically see what the item looks like
and how it's been sold over time.
And then it also has a deterministic pricing engine
so we can have the best price sold
and so that people can actually have
the most fair price for the items
and actually have some money back.
We also use BlueBubbles to test our software in general.
BlueBubbles is an iMessage software
that helps you text yourself or have your friend text you
so that you can demo the product.
One thing that separates Liquid
from other sales agents out there
is that we have our own pricing engine,
which takes in all different data points from Apify.
So we scrape active and sold listings.
Then we find out whether or not there was specific copy
or specific keywords,
or there was a certain price
that people sold something for.
And then we go and price your product at the same
or depending on how fast you want to sell your product,
more or less in price.